

# Nguyễn Mạnh Hùng

## Flutter Developer

**Phone:** 0909139618

Email: NguyenManhHung571999@gmail.com

Website: https://github.com/HungNguyen571999

Address: HoChiMinh, VietNam

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a Flutter developer with a lot of experience working on many large scale projects at home and abroad. I would like to apply my obtained knowledge and improve my passion skill in the professional working environment. Besides, I would like to create quality products with beautiful interfaces and give customers the most complete product.

#### **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2022

**Hoa Sen University** 

Major: Software Engineer Graduation rating: Good

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

May 2022 - Present

#### **Nexle Corporation**

Flutter Developer

- Support and guide member to build a team which is able to perform tasks.
- Develop and maintain mobile functionality of app screens.
- Engage in discussions with customers to clarify what they want.
- Have experience implement and architecting codebase for Flutter project with Bloc pattern.
- Investigate and fix bug from customer and QC complaints.
- Responsible for working on multiple projects at the same time.
- Integrate third-party technology services (Google maps, Firebase, ...) into the system.

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

### Eplus.vn

Flutter Developer

- · Research about Bloc Pattern.
- Build complete application interfaces with Flutter components.
- · Research about architecture of project Flutter.
- Implement RESTful API call base-on API documentation.
- · Participate in brainstorming sessions to brainstorm ideas.

Dec 2020 - Apr 2021

#### **ITSS training**

Frontend Developer

- Implement UI base-on Figma design, systemize Angular web component.
- Design website by Figma.
- Learning Spring boot and Spring Data JPA implement custom JPA Reponsitory.

#### **PROJECT**

Dec 2022 - Present

Name: My Thaco

**Position:** Flutter Developer **Customer:** THACO Group

**Description:** MyThaco is an internal application that allows users to view and interact directly with the latest news about the corporation. Besides, MyThaco is also a basic chat app that helps employees in THACO group easily connect with each other through conversation groups.

#### Responsibilities:

- · Deploy a Flutter project from scratch.
- Develop features according to project scope.
- · Investigate and fix bugs.
- · Review code and PR.
- · Link download app:
  - Apple Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/my-thaco/id1660844894
  - Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=vn.com.thaco.mythaco&;hl=en&gl=US

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

Name: Powerhub

Position: Flutter Developer

**Customer:** Nexle

**Description:** Powerhub is an application that allows you to track projects installed with IOT devices from the parent company.

#### Responsibilities:

- Implement new user story (Feature)
- Implement UI base-on Adobe XD design.
- Draw data chart and graph have provided by IoT devices.

May 2022 - Aug 2022

Name: T Fitness

**Position:** Flutter Developer

Customer: Thanda Hlaing (Myanmar)

**Description:** TFitness, the first personal training app in Myanmar, provides the latest health and fitness information and guidance. At the same time, build daily exercises that are evaluated by fitness experts.

#### Responsibilities:

- · Maintenance and fix bugs features (developed).
- Research about GetX to state management for app.
- · Implement new features.
- Link download app:
  - Apple Store: https://apps.apple.com/mm/app/tfitness/id1477288898
  - Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.OP.TFitness

Mar 2022 - Jul 2022

Name: Gateway

Position: Flutter Developer

**Customer:** Google Solution Challenge

**Description:** Gateway is an open-source solution for Covid 19 situation. Ours goal is provide solution for those 4 major pillar recommended by WHO.

#### Responsibilities:

- Contribute and design story board of the app in Figma.
- Implement UI and basic features according to project scope(ex: Handle permission camera, change language,..).

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

Name: Timebit OTC

Position: Flutter Developer

Customer: Eplus.vn

**Description:** TimebitOTC is an application that allows you to withdraw and deposit cryptocurrency anywhere on the blockchain network and exchange it with any bank in the world.

Responsibilities:

- · Maintenance and fix bugs UI.
- · Research about Bloc Pattern to state management for app.
- · Handle dummy data to implement UI.
- Link download app:
  - Apple Store: https://apps.apple.com/vn/app/timebit-otc/id1586916545
  - Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=sg.timebit.otc

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

Name: NextWord

**Position:** Flutter Developer Customer: Side with colleagues

Description: Multiplayer game with English word for English e-learning, The app located on app

store Android/IOS/Web.

#### Responsibilities:

- Design and implement storyboard UI/UX in Figma.
- Running social campaign marketing product to potential customers/users.
- Manage in-app advisement by using Google Admob.
- Restful API CRUD data by server send up.
- Support implement in app state management solution using Bloc pattern.
- · Link download app:
  - Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nextword.nextword
  - Apple Store: https://apps.apple.com/vn/app/nextword/id1586762180?l=vi

#### **ACTIVITIES**

10/2019 - Present

#### **Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC)**

Core team member

- · Contribute ideas, build the development orientation of the club.
- · Participating in sharing learning experiences as well as personal knowledge with other members of the club (Internal training).
- · Several workshops were held:
  - · Git/Github
  - Flutter study jam

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

2022	Top 3 Google Solution Challenge winner
2020 - 2021	Google Developer Student Clubs Community Core Team
2019	Aptis Certificate of British Council - B1

SKILLS	
Soft skills	Patient, Teamwork, Problem solving and Time management
Technology	Flutter, Firebase
Language	Vietnamese, English

#### **REFERENCES**

Certifications are located: https://github.com/HungNguyen571999/Cretifications-and-honour

 $Information\ about\ google\ solution\ contest:\ https://docs.google.com/document/d/1zYfxmz5INuRjKym-azOSDx4P1AmgmvpcQK6sCCQVQdU/edit?fbclid=IwAR3HAuYeS1TfH3aDqZ5FFRqiDqpQtNXrN7hOtrmKkf-nOEegAeMBOTtKlf8$